{
    "id": "23c66923ea6f4fe5819a3312a9b4c19e",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Manchester is known ……………….. its textile industry.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The goat subsists ………………… leaves.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "on",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is quite fond ………………. her grandchildren.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "off",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It is natural for men to wish ………………. distinction.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "at",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "It is evident that he is enamored ………………… her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Ambition does not always conduce ………………. happiness.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Nowadays computers are cheap enough to be accessible ………………… most people.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A gentleman is courteous ……………… his neighbors.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am indebted ………………. you for your help.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "People who are averse ……………….. hard work do not succeed in life.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "There is no cure ………………. the common cold.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The noise from upstairs prevented me ………………… sleeping.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}